

JENNIFER BUNNER

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Html & Css/Sass/Scss

lavascript

React.js, Vue.js

Quasar

Node.js

Express.js, npm

jQuery, MVC

Graphic design & UX-design

PHP, Wordpress

Databases:

MySql, noSQL, sql, crud

Firebase, Firestore

A JAX, JSON, REST

Api, Github, Git

Visual Studio Code

Figma, Zeplin, Agila metoder,

Scrum

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Svenska -moder tongue

Engelska - fluent

Franska - light conversation

Spanska - light conversation

CONTACT

Email

bunner.jennifer@gmail.com

Telefonnummer 0735 122431

linkedin.com/in/jenniferbunner810 github.com/iths-jennifer-bunner

ABOUT ME

After many years in the trade and as a Visual Merchandiser, I have now got my diploma in frontend development at the IT-Högskolan.

With knowledge such as teamwork, problem solving and communication as well as an eye for detail, I am used to working at a fast pace and stressful situations. I am flexible and like to come along and try new ideas.

Portfolio page: https://www.jenniferbunner.com/

EDUCATION

IT HÖGSKOLAN 2019-2021

Frontend developer. See Technical Knowledge to see what I have studied.

INTERNSHIP 2

ZIGNSEC V6-20 2021

I was commissioned to make a new portal with improved UI, than the existing one written in Angular, with the aim that the new portal will start to be used on their new platform, I have together with another student designed mockups to code the portal in React.js, Sass, and material.ui. We worked towards an API on their existing database to retrieve information

INTERNSHIP 1

EVIDENT (HTTPS://EVIDENT.CAPITAL/) V34-41 2020

A startup in the fintech industry. Where I had the main responsibility for making their marketing page (from design to deployment). Available at: https://bocapital.se/ I have designed the page in figma and then coded it in vue.js using Quasar framework and Sass / scss. Have translated it using i18n and installed mailchimp.



JENNIFER BUNNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

GINA TRICOT

Visual merchandiser 100406-ongoing

Responsible for Gina tricot's concept being visualized and optimized in the store. Store windows (styling, decoration), styling mannequins, campaign follow-up, placement of goods and work with different surfaces in the store, work with purchase proposals, follow-up of sales and make sure the right product is in the right place, inform staff about our campaigns and trends. Helped to open new stores and at new openings.

MANGO

Visual merchandiser 070801-100401

As part of the management team, I was responsible for the visuals inside the store. Prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store and style mannequins. Responsible for achieving sales goals and making analyzes of sales. Inform the staff about trends and our campaigns. Hold meetings on upcoming trends and materials science.

MQ

Visual merchandiser 040201-070713

Responsible for shop windows and all mannequins. Responsible for the visuals in the store, prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store. Helped to open new stores and at new openings in other stores. Inform the staff about our campaigns and trends.

ΜQ

Säljare 030122-040201

Responsible for complaints and returns. Buyers for accessories (scarves, scarves and belts from the brand Atlas), and for Fornarina. Managed the store's clearings (send returns and complaints back to the dealer.

OTHER EDUCATION

FOLKUNIVERSITET; 2008

Drawing and kroki

FOLKUNIVERSITETET; 2008

Illustration

COURS DE CIVILISATION FRANCAIS DE LA SORBONNE; 2009-2010

FRANS SCHARTAU; 2009-2010

Business administration

ENSKILDA GYMNASIET; 1995-2000

Secondary school and Socio-economic program - upper secondary diploma

REFERENCES

Given at request